Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, Part III, 1930-2006 MS2394
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Walter E. Fauntroy and Associates files, 1981-2006; 1994-1999; MS2394 Series 2
  - Timetables [New Birth Correctional Facility], 1995; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Treatment [Prision Treatment Programs], 1995; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - United House of Prayer, 1994, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Universal Declaration [on the Sovereignty of the Human Person Under God], 1997 July; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Urban Inter-Faith Finanical Network - Mike Morris, 2004; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy & Associates Correspondence, 1993; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy Associates - Haiti Initiave, 1995; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy & Associates - Stationary, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy (Bio) Curriculum Vita, 1999, 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy - Prayers Against Profiling (Muslims), 2006 November 28; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Washington Hosptial Center Board, 2005 May 13; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wfauntory Speaking Engagements, 2005-2006; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Who Killed the Middle Class?" From The New Yorker, 1995 October 16; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - World Bank [Public Information Center], 1995-1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - WORLD COM, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - World Vision, 1994 November 1; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - WPFW Items [Investigations of Black Politicians], 1995, 1998, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Zaire [African Issues], 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Zimbabwe [Namibian Catholic Bishop's Conference], 2001, 2003; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- New Bethel Baptist Church materials, 1930-2005; 1955-1997; MS2394 Series 3
  - Evangelism - Visitation [Religious Teaching Materials], 1997, 2005; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Interdenominational Minister's Alliance/Urban Renewal, 1960, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Misc. [Speeches and Sermons], undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Music Department, 1963-1975, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Music [Religious Sheet Music], circa 1930s-1960s, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Musicians' Job Descriptions, 1983; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NBBC Ministers' Meetings, 1974, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - 20-Year Plan (2004-2024), 1970, 2003, 2004, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church Facilities Use Forms, circa 1980s, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church Labels, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - Officers (2004) [Installation Service for Church Leaders], 2004 January 25; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - Position Descriptions (Minister of Music), 1999; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - The Rapture ["The Rapture" by Cynthia Whitehead], 1994, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - Spiritual Renewal, 1997; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - Spiritual Renewal Program, Pt. 2, 1997; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - True Family Values [1/2], 1996-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - New Bethel Baptist Church - True Family Values [2/2], 1996-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Old Constitution, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Our Pastor's Thirty-First Anniversary Celebration - The First Family, 1990 March; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Parsonage [Receipts], 1962, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Proposal Brochure - 1960, 1960, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Rogers Legal Services [Seminar for Members], 1995 November 11, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sermon Garden [Sermons, Correspondence and other Church documents], 1959, 2000, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Souvenir Programme Installation Services for The Reverand Walter E. Fauntroy, 1959; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meeting Memorandum, November 8, 1990, 1990 November 15; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Suffering [Handwritten notes], undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The First Lady's Scholars Banquet, 1988; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "The Lord - Papers Pertaining to the Lord [Religious teachings material], 1996-1999, undated; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Obituraries and Funeral Programs by Rev. W. E. Fauntroy [1/2], 1955-1970, 1973-1979, 1982-1983, 1995; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Obituraries and Funeral Programs by Rev. W. E. Fauntroy [2/2], 1955-1970, 1973-1979, 1982-1983, 1995; MS2394 Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)